Hello.
こんにちは
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
やりかく可愛いな
Hello, I'm finally done.
どうも、やっとるよ
Do you have long experience?
長い経験ですか?
It's science.
理科です
理科じゃん
It's science.
理科です
Science, how old are you now?
理科じゃん、今何歳ですか?
I'm 19 years old.
19歳です
It's red.
赤いっすね
Are you 19 years old?
19歳か
By the way, are you 19 years old?
ちなみに、19歳ってこと?
university student?
大学生?
No, I'm a high school graduate and I work in a fleet.
いや、高卒でフリートはやってます
You're already out in society.
もう 社会に出てるね
Fleet, by the way, can I ask what kind of part-time job you have?
フリート、ちなみに何のバイトとかって聞いてもいい?
I work as a hall staff at a restaurant.
飲食店でホールスタッフしてます
Are you a waiter?
ウエイトレスターですか?
Well then, let's talk about that waiter's safety again this time.
じゃあちょっと今度もそのウエイトレスターのセフで
please.
お願いします
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Please ask me if I've kept you waiting.
お待たせしましたって聞いてよ
Isn't that what Obomo is like?
オボモって、そんな感じじゃない?
Is it different?
違うの?
So, you're Fleet Assan now, and who's your boyfriend?
じゃあ今フリートあさんで、彼氏さんは?
I'm not there.
いないです
Are you not there?
いないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
How cute is this?
こんな可愛いの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
She's so cute, but doesn't she have a boyfriend?
こんな可愛いのに、彼氏いないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
Well, I don't have a boyfriend.
じゃあ彼氏はいないけど
So, do you have any naughty friends?
じゃあ、エッチな友達ありますか?
now.
今
Do you have a sex friend?
セフレいるの?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いないのに?
I don't have a boyfriend so I'm a sex friend.
彼氏いないからセフレ
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
I see.
なるほどね
I said it wrong.
言い方が間違ってた
that's right.
そうです
The grammar was wrong.
文法が間違ってた
By the way, do you have only one sex friend?
ちなみにセフレは一人ですか?
Two people.
二人
Isn't it just a helper?
ただの助け身じゃないか
There are two sex friends.
セフレは二人
Two people.
二人
Have you ever been in any unusual positions with those sex friends?
そのセフレさん達とは、変わった位置とかはしたことありますか?
Well, well.
まあ、まあ
3P or something.
3Pとか
3P?
Did you have a threesome?
3Pした?
3P
Is that with that sex friend No. 1 and No. 2?
それはそのセフレ一号二号と?
No.
違います
Did sex friend No. 1 call a friend?
セフレ一号が仲間を呼んだんですか?
friend.
友達
Drinking friends.
呑み友達
Did you have drinking friends?
呑み友達ってやったの?
Drinking friends?
呑み友達?
In a drunken state?
酔った勢いで?
I agree.
そうですね
I think it was because I was so livid.
ベロベロだったからみたいな
Beloved.
ベロベロ
Are you trying to apologize because you were drunk?
酔ってたからですまそうとしちゃう?
I think it was because I was drunk.
酔ってたからみたいな
I say this because it's cute.
可愛いから言うけどさ
No, you can't do it like that when you're drunk.
ダメよ、そんな酔っ払って勢いでやっちゃう
By the way, do you do anything else outside?
ちなみに他は、お外でやったりとかないの?
No, but only the butt.
はないですけど、あとお尻だけ
Butt?
お尻?
Only once.
一回だけ
Did you do it in your butt?
お尻でやったんですか?
Only once.
一回だけ
Try it.
試しに
Only once?
一回だけ?
Only once.
一回だけ
Today is?
今日は?
Today is normal.
今日は普通に
Is it normal today?
今日は普通に?
Normally.
普通に
Sex?
セックス?
sex.
セックス
Can you do that for me?
してくれますか?
I agree.
そうですね
It wasn't good either.
いいともじゃなかった
So, I can't help you unless you tell me if you can give it to me.
で、くれるかなって言ってくれないといいともでないです
Sorry.
すいません
Well then, I really like it.
じゃあ、えっちゃ好きなんだ
I agree.
そうですね
Really.
わりと
Really?
わりと?
Really.
わりと
I think I like it a lot.
かなり好きだと思うな
As it is?
それなりに?
In its own way.
それなりにね
She's a cute girl and looks like she has good style,
可愛い子で、こんなスタイル良さそうな子が、
It's great that you like Edge.
エッジ好きなんて、最高ですね
Highest.
最高
Well, today I would like to do something more edgy.
じゃあ、今日はもっとエッジなことをしていきたいと思います
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Will you do your best?
頑張ってくれる?
I'll do my best and have fun.
頑張って楽しみます
English.
英語や
Today's child speaks a lot of English.
今日の子、めっちゃ英語や
Well, thank you very much.
じゃあ、よろしくお願いします
Oh no, this.
やだな、これ
picture?
え?
what?
なに?
I can see mine.
自分のやつ見えるんだよ
I don't like seeing it.
見えてるの嫌だな
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Don't you hate it? Maybe you don't like the way you see yourself on the screen.
なんか嫌じゃないですか、画面で撮ってる自分が嫌かも
Eh, is that so?
えー、そうなの?
Is that so?
そんなの?
I just touch it normally.
とか普通に触ってるけど
Huh?
あれ?
Are your breasts getting bigger?
おっぱい大きくなっちゃってる?
No, that's not true.
いや、そんなことないよ
Not that much?
そんなにない?
so.
そんなに
There is quite a difference with the under...
アンダーとの差が結構...
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
Is the underside thin?
アンダーが細いのか
There's no top at all.
トップとかは全然ないでしょ
Not at all.
全然ない
Not at all?
全然ないんですか?
Not at all.
全然ないですよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Not at all, not at all.
全然、全然、全然
I'm trying to hide it with my legs.
足で隠そうとしてる
Did you find out?
バレた?
It's obvious, it's obvious.
バレてる、バレてる
I just don't think I can see it.
ちょうど見えないかなと
It's just, it's just hidden.
ちょうどね、ちょうど隠れてるね
I can't see my fingering at all.
この、俺の指使いが全く見えない
It's completely guarded, right?
完全にガードしてるでしょ、これも
I'm guarding.
ガードしてる
Skin is smooth.
肌すべす
Go to the bottom page.
下ページして
Earrings for you.
ピアスついとりあなた
I thought that too.
俺もあれって思ってた
I'm on the bottom page.
下ページしてます
Are you on the bottom page?
下ページしてるの?
I haven't heard it.
聞いてないよ
Say it, say it, say it.
言って、言った、言って
Did you say it?
言った?
Really?
本当に?
I heard it wrong.
俺聞き間違えた
Did I hear it wrong?
聞き間違えたか
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
Be stable.
安定して
It's kind of scary.
なんかやばい
It's scary to be watched.
眺められてるのやばい
Very, very erotic, comment.
めっちゃ、めっちゃエロいわ、コメント
I'll do it here too.
こっちにもする
perfume.
香水
Gappana.
ガッパーナ
Gappana is also a perfume.
ガッパーナも香水
Not Gappana.
ガッパーナじゃない
It's not the perfume's fault.
香水のせいじゃない
What a cute person.
かわいい人やな
Uncle did shit.
おじさんくそやった
It's here.
きたね
I noticed.
気づいた
Because I was hurt.
傷ついたから
傷ついちゃったからさ
What about promotion?
昇進は?
I'm getting a promotion, so please show me your bra.
昇進なんで、ちょっとブラジャー見せてください
I see.
なるほどね
This is what you were wearing.
こういうの着てたんだね
That's right.
そうで
It's definitely a one-piece dress.
てっきりワンピースなの
I said buchi.
ブチって言った
Did you say spotty?
ブチって言った?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Dangerous, dangerous.
危ない、危ない
For now, yes.
とりあえず、はい
Take it off.
脱いで
By yourself?
自分で?
Take it off.
脱いで
Show me your fresh clothes.
生着替えを見せて
Well then, I'll have this.
じゃあ、こちらいただきます
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Later, you will have delicious safu.
後でサフがおいしくいただいてきます
Please let me take it home.
持って帰らせてください
As much as possible.
できるだけ
By the time I get home, I won't be able to finish it.
帰るときは、きれなくなっちゃうからね
When I go home, I can't finish it.
帰るとき、きれなくなっちゃう
As expected, the style is nice.
やっぱ、スタイルいいよね
But it's a little lumpy.
でも、若干ぽよぽよ
It's not swollen, at all.
ぽよぽしてないよ、全然
Is it bulging?
ぽよぽよしてる?
The old man is chubby,
おっさんのほうがぽよぽよしてるよ、
this.
これ
Panpan.
パンパン
Don't say pan-pan, just a little.
パンパンって言わないで、ちょっと
Isn't it chubby?
ぽよぽよではない?
It's not chubby.
ぽよぽよではない
Panpan.
パ ンパン
Let's punch it later.
後でパンパンしよう
I can't say it myself.
自分で言ってしょうもない
Seriously.
マジで
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
I get angry.
怒られちゃう
Perverted uncle.
変 態おじさん
Who is the pervert uncle?
誰が変態おじさん?
I'm sure he's an old man.
確かにおじさんだけど
Soft chest.
胸柔らか
Wait a minute, what is this now?
ちょっと待って、今のこれ何ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Wait a minute, aren't you already feeling tingly?
ちょっと待って、すでにさ、 チクビ立ってきてませんか?
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
気のせいなの
Originally it was like this.
もともとこんな感じ
Is the child originally standing?
もともと立ってる子なの?
oh yeah.
そうそう
I see.
なるほど
Shirokujichu.
しろくじちゅう
A child standing all the time.
しろくじちゅう立ってる子
He's just a pervert, that's all.
ただの変態やん、そんなの
Shirokujichu.
しろくじちゅう
What a child standing up stiffly.
し ろ く じ ち ゅ う、チクビ立ってる子なんて
Are you the governor's woman?
知事女ですか?
No.
違います
Are you responsible for the governor's wife's household finances?
知事女の家計の方ですか?
No.
違います
Oh, beautiful breasts.
あら、きれいなおっぱい
Well, the old man will wear this later.
じゃあ、これは後でおじさんがかぶってなります
Please return it.
返してください
Do you want it back?
返してほしいですか?
I want it back.
返してほしい
It's really a pen computer.
ほんとペンコンなんだね
Raise your face.
顔あげて
yeah?
ん?
You may not be able to see her cute face at all.
可愛い顔が全く見えないかもしれない
I don't like having my face seen.
顔見られるのが苦手なんですよ
You look cute.
可愛い顔してるんだね
Just being bright is fine.
明るいだけでいいやろ
Don't you like it just because it's bright?
明るいだけで嫌なの?
Who is the cheerful old man?
明るいおじさんは?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
The only thing that makes it bright is its brightness.
明るいだけが取り柄なのに
I might not like it.
嫌かも
Eh, is that so?
えー、そうなの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Cute, cute.
可愛い可愛い
It's really damp.
すごい湿ってるんだ
I'm so scared.
めっちゃビケる
I think it's already getting damp.
なんかもう湿ってきてるんじゃないか、
Just this.
ちょっとこれ
It's getting a bit damp, isn't it?
湿ってきてるよね、ちょっと
mosquito
か
Before it breaks.
つ て折れちゃう前に
I don't want you to see it.
見ないで欲しい
I totally want you not to look at me, I'm not so tight anymore
見ないで欲しいって完全だって、もうぴっちゃびちゃじゃないっす
hey.
ね
Hasn't this come in?
これ 入ってきてないの?
Maybe not yet.
もしかして、まだ
Hair removal.
脱毛
Oh, really?
え、ほんとに?
Because I was losing hair.
脱毛いってたから
You haven't lost your hair, you're beautiful.
脱毛いってないでしょ、綺麗だよ、
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
Hair removal means shaving.
脱毛いって、剃ってる
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
Ah, I thought you weren't born yet.
あ、まだ生えてない方かと思いました
I got really wet.
ガチでびちゃびちゃになっちゃった
And it closed perfectly.
しかもぴったり閉じちゃって
It's seriously erotic.
ガチでエロいね
This is seriously private and there's nothing you can do about it.
これマジでプライベートでどうしようもいらないでしょ
I don't need it.
いらない
Well then, let's push through here a little bit.
じゃあさ、ちょっとこっちに押し抜けさ、
Fourth.
4つ目
Let's touch this side a little more.
もうちょっとこっち側に手つける
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Because I'm reading it all at once.
一気に俺が読んでるから
Too erotic.
エロすぎ
It's just a little too erotic.
エロすぎるからさ、ちょっとさ
Okay.
よ い しょ
Too erotic.
エロすぎ
It felt so good that I came out a little.
気持ち良すぎてちょっと出ちゃった
This direction looks dangerous.
この向きがヤバそう
Is it dangerous?
ヤバい?
Big.
おっきい
Oh no, I'm starting to lose my patience.
やばい、ちょっと我慢できなくなってきちゃった
Can I put it in?
入れてもいい?
this.
これ
Ku
く
stomach.
い
Okay.
よ いしょ
eye
め
It's gone.
っちゃ 出ちゃった
It felt good.
気持ち良かった
It's too erotic.
エロすぎです
Will you have sex with me?
エッチしてくれる?
Okay.
いいよ